Clief Notes: 📚Navigating The Course

Hello, everyone I just wanted to make a video that would describe how to navigate this community as well as what the leaderboards and point systems look like, and how you can actually win money at the end of each month by being at the top of the leaderboard, but first I want to just dive into the community, it's tab now in the community tab, obviously you have posts from me and Matt, but you also have posts from a lot of amazing other people who are either sharing good news about how they secured clients from the knowledge that they've been learning or just people asking for help under the troubleshooting tab. 

Now you cannot post immediately when you come to the community, you actually need to get to level 2 1st, and you will see that we actually have badges for each level, and these are title unlocks. And these courses let you know what level you're at very quickly, or you can actually go to the leaderboards and see where your level is, how many points you need to make and kind of what's going on there. You'll also be able to see different unlocks for those levels inside of the getting started room where we describe a bit more about the levels what you get for each one and how you can actually end up with a $500 reward for reaching level 9 or even getting lifetime access to our volts and paid content at level 8, but let's say you're just starting out, you're not wanting to worry about doing paid contents content, which if you do want to upgrade it's simply right here, we do not require it. 

We allow all of those access to 34 lessons everywhere else easily quickly, but you can just upgrade right there with a link on the left. But once you hit level 2, you can actually post, you can add attachments. Whatever you would like there, you can share links YouTube videos polls you can even add titles and we have various categories for different things as resources or wins or showing your work when you're going inside of the classroom, let's say you're inside a foundation one of our main classrooms where I'm constantly adding foundational knowledge stuff that you could watch in 10 years and still get value from, you'll actually notice that there's a check mark that you can click to show that you're completed that affects your percentage done. 

Please check those any chance you get, but at the bottom of each lesson, we have check INS where people can vote on kind of what is going on. You can see how other people are doing it as well as comments or questions that I all constantly try to respond to when I have time, and as you can see, some of these lessons have completely changed the way people see things. One of my favorite tabs is the map tab, actually, and this is the last thing I'll leave you with, which is this amazing, amazing map of some of our members from all around the world. 

So if you see a notice that there's people from, maybe somewhere where you are, it was always nice to go check. In, it doesn't give you your exact location, but it gives you an idea of roughly where you are so you can go ahead and see if there's anyone in the community in your neck of the woods, other than that, I hope you all enjoy dive in and learn as much as possible. I'm excited to have you here and can't wait to see how you all contribute. 
